<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Amelia Kwan</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Amelia Kwan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Translayte | Personalized Translation Software</title>
      <link>/custom2/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom2/post1/</guid>
      <description>Translayte is a school project I&amp;rsquo;m working on with some other students using Google&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Translation API for our Software Design course. We&amp;rsquo;re using Java, JUnit for testing, and Java Swing for the interface, and the goal is to have a well-functioning software that adheres to Clean Architecture and SOLID principles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arduino Robot Arm &amp; Remote-Controlled Car</title>
      <link>/custom2/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom2/post3/</guid>
      <description>I worked on this project just this summer after wanting to explore the hardware side of technology - I taught myself Arduino IDE and programming language, creating and designing an iPhone remote-controlled car utilizing dabble, Arduino UNO Rev3, Bluetooth Module, Motor Drive Controller and created a simple dial-controlled robot arm using Arduino UNO Rev3, and 4 servo motors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ParaHunt | Scroller Game</title>
      <link>/custom2/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom2/post4/</guid>
      <description>This is my first big project! I worked on it at the end of high school. It&amp;rsquo;s a scroller game featuring the player as a hamster falling with a parachute, and the goal is to collect cupcakes as he parachutes down while making sure to avoid the evil flying jellyfish in the sky. It&amp;rsquo;s coded in Python using the Pygame library, and I drew all of the sprites and backgrounds by myself!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
