<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Amelia Kwan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amelia Kwan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Director | Youth In Politics</title>
      <link>/custom1/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom1/post2/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always had a passion for writing, as well as global issues surrounding human rights, culture, technology, and politics, so much so that Journalism was actually my second choice for my post-secondary education. I loved watching Johnny Harris videos, reading articles, and debating with my friends about what was going on in the world - and I was fortunate to have the opportunity to be part of something bigger, and to produce the same kind of content I was consuming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Translayte | Personalized Translation Software</title>
      <link>/custom2/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom2/post1/</guid>
      <description>Translayte is a school project I&amp;rsquo;m working on with some other students using Google&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Translation API for our Software Design course. We&amp;rsquo;re using Java, JUnit for testing, and Java Swing for the interface, and the goal is to have a well-functioning software that adheres to Clean Architecture and SOLID principles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arduino Robot Arm &amp; Remote-Controlled Car</title>
      <link>/custom2/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom2/post3/</guid>
      <description>I worked on this project just this summer after wanting to explore the hardware side of technology - I taught myself Arduino IDE and programming language, creating and designing an iPhone remote-controlled car utilizing dabble, Arduino UNO Rev3, Bluetooth Module, Motor Drive Controller and created a simple dial-controlled robot arm using Arduino UNO Rev3, and 4 servo motors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitchen Staff | Sansotei Ramen</title>
      <link>/custom1/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom1/post1/</guid>
      <description>This was my first &amp;ldquo;real job&amp;rdquo;, my first experience working full-time, and my first experience working in a restaurant. I loved learning about the craft of ramen, the workflow of a kitchen and its staff, how inventory is managed, and working alongside many other people to make it happen.
At Sansotei, the kitchen staff were in charge of everything in the back - from managing inventory and preparing food to dishwashing and cleaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High School Tutor | Teenage Tutors</title>
      <link>/custom1/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom1/post3/</guid>
      <description>Being a tutor, and being able to mentor and teach others never felt like a job to me. Every student is unique, with their own strengths and challenges, and I loved the process of tailoring my teaching approach to each one. I&amp;rsquo;ve had so many amazing mentors in my own life, and I wanted to do the exact same for others as well.
This experience truly honed my communication and interpersonal skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ParaHunt | Scroller Game</title>
      <link>/custom2/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom2/post4/</guid>
      <description>This is my first big project! I worked on it at the end of high school. It&amp;rsquo;s a scroller game featuring the player as a hamster falling with a parachute, and the goal is to collect cupcakes as he parachutes down while making sure to avoid the evil flying jellyfish in the sky. It&amp;rsquo;s coded in Python using the Pygame library, and I drew all of the sprites and backgrounds by myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>about</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
